[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What did the ocean say to the shore?",
    "answer": "Nothing, it just waved."
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Why don't skeletons fight each other?",
    "answer": "They don't have the guts."
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Why was the math book sad?",
    "answer": "Because it had too many problems."
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Where do programmers like to hangout?",
    "answer": "The Foo Bar."
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Why did the opera singer go sailing?",
    "answer": "They wanted to hit the high Cs."
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Why did the half blind man fall in the well?",
    "answer": "Because he couldn't see that well!"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What did the Zen Buddist say to the hotdog vendor?",
    "answer": "Make me one with everything."
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "A programmer puts two glasses on his bedside table before going to sleep.",
    "answer": "A full one, in case he gets thirsty, and an empty one, in case he doesnâ€™t."
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Why did the programmer quit his job?",
    "answer": "Because he didn't get arrays."
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What did one plate say to the other plate?",
    "answer": "Dinner is on me!"
  }
]
